<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Table Name="ENHANCED MR IMAGE MODULE ATTRIBUTES" Table="C.8-79">
<!--Attribute Name 	Tag 	Type  Attribute Description-->
<!--Include ' MR Image and Spectroscopy Instance  Macro' Table C.8-81 -->
<Entry Tag="(0008,0008)" Attribute="Image Type" Type="1" Description="Image characteristics.">
  <Reference Table="C.8.16.1">
  <Reference Table="C.8.13.3.1.1">
</Entry>
<!--Include Common CT/MR Image Description Macro' Table C.8.131  -->
<!--Include 'MR Image Description Macro' Table C.8.82 	 -->
Samples per Pixel 	(0028,0002)  	1 	Number of samples (planes) in this image.  This value shall be 1. 
Photometric Interpretation 	(0028,0004)  	1 	Specifies the intended interpretation of the pixel data. Enumerated Value:  MONOCHROME2. See C.7.6.3.1.2 for  definition of this term. 
Bits Allocated 	(0028,0100) 	1 	Number of bits allocated for each pixel sample. Each sample shall have the same  number of bits allocated. Enumerated  Values: 8 and 16. 
Bits Stored 	(0028,0101) 	1 	Number of bits stored for each pixel sample. Each sample shall have the same  number of bits stored. Enumerated  	Values: 8, 12 and 16. See C.8.13.1.1.1 for  specialization. 
High Bit 	(0028,0102) 	1 	Most significant bit for pixel sample data.  Each sample shall have the same high bit.  Shall be one less than the value in Bits  Stored (0028,0101). 
Spacing between Slices 	(0018,0088) 	3 	Value of the prescribed spacing to be applied between the slices in a volume  		that is to be acquired. The spacing in mm  		is defined as the center-to-center distance  of adjacent slices. 
Lossy Image Compression 	(0028,2110) 	1 	Specifies whether an Image has undergone lossy compression.  Enumerated Values:  		00 =  Image has NOT been  			subjected to lossy  			compression.  		01 =  Image has been subjected  			to lossy compression.  See C.7.6.1.1.5 for further explanation. 
Lossy Image Compression Ratio 	(0028,2112) 	1C 	Describes the approximate lossy compression ratio(s) that have been  applied to this image.  See C.7.6.1.1.5 for further explanation.  May be multivalued if successive lossy  compression steps have been applied.  Note: 	For example, a compression ratio 
of 30:1 would be described in this  Attribute with a single value of 30.  Required if Lossy Images Compression  (0028,2110) is “01”. 
Lossy Image Compression Method 	(0028,2114) 	1C 	A label for the lossy compression method(s) that have been applied to this  image.  See C.7.6.1.1.5 for further explanation.  May be multivalued if successive lossy  		compression steps have been applied; the  		value order shall correspond to the values  of Lossy Image Compression Ratio  (0028,2112).  Required if Lossy Image Compression  (0028,2110) is “01”. 
Presentation LUT Shape 	(2050,0020) 	1 	Specifies an identity transformation for the Presentation LUT, such that the output of  all grayscale transformations defined in  the IOD containing this Module are  defined to be P-Values.  Enumerated Values:  IDENTITY - output is in P-Values. 
Icon Image Sequence 	(0088,0200) 	3 	This icon image is representative of the Image. 
<!--> Include ‘Image Pixel Macro’ Table C.7-11b 	See Section F.7. -->


</Table>
